Guide to the Karen Halverson Photographs of the American West
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Photographs of the American West.
1987-2011
WA Photos Folio 75
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
101.3
(31 boxes)
This collection includes portfolios of photographs and panoramic photographs created by Halverson that document the American West, 1987-2011.
200 prints: inkjet, color; 61.0 x 50.8 cm.
12 prints: inkjet, color; 40.6 x 121.9 cm.
1 volume; 22 cm
Halverson, Karen, 1941-
General note
Title devised by cataloger.
General note
Stored in 31 boxes.
General note
Each portfolio consists of 60 inkjet prints, 61.0 x 50.8 cm., and 4 inkjet prints, 40.6 x 121.9 cm, except for the Dakota Survey, which consists of 20 inkjet prints, 61.0 x 50.8 cm.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Karen Halverson on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2010-2016.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Karen Halverson (born 1941)
Karen Halverson is a documentary landscape photographer. Born in Syracuse, New York, Halverson received a Bachelor of Arts from Stanford University and Masters of Arts from Brandeis University and Columbia University. In 1975, she made her first photographic project, which documented the Garment District in New York City. Much of her work documents the tension between the natural and cultural landscapes of the American West. She is the author of Downstream: Encounters with the Colorado River (University of California Press, 2008), which retraces the route of John Wesley Powell's expeditions and explores what contemporary Americans have made of the waterway.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes portfolios of photographs and panoramic photographs created by Halverson that document the American West, 1987-2011.
Photographs of the Colorado River, 1994-1995, chronicle Halverson's exploration of the river from its tributaries, the Gunnison River and Green River, through its main length, including sites along the river in Wyoming, Colorado, Utah, Arizona, Nevada, California, and Sonora, Mexico.
Photographs of Basin & Range, 1987-2004, consists of images created by Halverson that explore a semiarid region of the western United States, also known as the Great Basin. This region extends from the Sierra Nevada on the west to the Wasatch Range on the east and from the Columbia Plateau in the north to the Mojave Desert in the south.
Mulholland: Nature and Culture in Los Angeles, 1991-2006, depicts views along Mulholland Highway and Mulholland Drive, a scenic road in Los Angeles County, California, that runs from California Highway 1 (Pacific Coast Highway) near Malibu along the crest of the Santa Monica Mountains to Hollywood.
Dakota Survey, 2011, depicts views of sites in North Dakota and South Dakota with an emphasis on lines and grids in the landscape.
Most photographs in the collection are color inkjet prints with dimensions of 61.0 x 50.8 centimeters, and the panoramic prints have dimensions 40.6 x 121.9 centimeters.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: I. The Colorado River, 1994-1995. II. Basin & Range, 1987-2004. III. Mulholland: Nature and Culture in Los Angeles, 1991-2006. IV. Dakota Survey, 2011.
Landscapes -- Colorado River Valley (Colo.-Mexico) -- Pictorial works; Natural history -- Colorado River Valley (Colo.-Mexico) -- Pictorial works; Reservoirs -- California -- Los Angeles County -- Pictorial works; Roads -- California -- Los Angeles County -- Pictorial works; Alabama Hills (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Arizona -- Pictorial works; Benson (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Beverly Glen (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Black Canyon (Ariz. and Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Bonneville Salt Flats (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Bowdle (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; Calabasas Highlands (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; California -- Pictorial works; California Highway 1 (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Canyonlands National Park (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Capitol Reef National Park (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Cataract Canyon (Wayne County-San Juan County, Utah) -- Pictorial works; Colorado River (Colo.-Mexico) -- Pictorial works; Colorado River Valley (Colo.-Mexico) -- Pictorial works; Cora (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Crescent Junction (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Davis Dam (Ariz. and Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Death Valley (Calif. and Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Death Valley Junction (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Desert Hot Springs (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Dickinson (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Dubois (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Dupuyer (Mont.) -- Pictorial works; Edmore (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Elko (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Factory Butte (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Flaming Gorge Reservoir (Wyo. and Utah) -- Pictorial works; Flasher (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; Fryman Canyon (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Garrison (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Glen Canyon Dam (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Grace City (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Grand Canyon (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Grand Lake (Colo.) -- Pictorial works; Great Basin -- Pictorial works; Great Salt Lake (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Great Salt Lake Desert (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Greybull (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Havasu, Lake (Ariz. and Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Heart Butte (Mont.) -- Pictorial works; Hite (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Hollywood (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Independence (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Kadoka (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; Keeler (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Laurel Canyon (Los Angeles, Calif.); Lennep (Mont.) -- Pictorial works; Leola (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; Lodore, Canyon of (Colo.) -- Pictorial works; Los Angeles County (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Max (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Mead, Lake (Ariz. and Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Mohave, Lake (Ariz. and Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Montana -- Pictorial works; Monument Valley (Ariz. and Utah) -- Pictorial works; Mulholland Drive (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Nevada -- Pictorial works; New Mexico -- Pictorial works; Newell (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; North Dakota -- Pictorial works; North Las Vegas (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Olancha (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Onida (S.D.) -- Pictorial works; Pacific Coast Highway -- Pictorial works; Parker Dam (Ariz. and Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Pinedale (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Powell, Lake (Utah and Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Price (Utah) -- Pictorial works; Pyramid Lake (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Quartzsite (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Reliance (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Rhyolite (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Rock Springs (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Rugby (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Runyon Canyon (Los Angeles, Calif.); Saline Valley (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Santa Monica Mountains (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Scenic (S.D.: Township) -- Pictorial works; Sentinel Butte (N.D.) -- Pictorial works; Shiprock (N.M.) -- Pictorial works; South Dakota -- Pictorial works; Thermopolis (Wyo.) -- Pictorial works; Tonopah (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Universal City (Calif.); Utah -- Pictorial works; Valley of the Gods (Utah) -- Pictorial works; West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; Wind River (Wyo.: River) -- Pictorial works; Winnemucca (Nev.) -- Pictorial works; Wyoming -- Pictorial works; Yellowstone National Park -- Pictorial works; Inkjet prints; Panoramas; Panoramic photographs; Photographic prints; Halverson, Karen, 1941-; Hollywood Bowl (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works
- The Colorado River, 1994-1995; Series I; 0.5; (6 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Arranged sequentially by numbers applied by Halverson, followed by panoramic photographs arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Photographs of the Colorado River, 1994-1995, chronicle Halverson's exploration of the river from its tributaries, the Gunnison River and Green River, through its main length, including sites along the river in Wyoming, Colorado, Utah, Arizona, Nevada, California, and Sonora, Mexico. Many of the images were published in her work, Downstream: Encounters with the Colorado River (Berkeley: University of California Press, 2008). Images of canyons include the Canyon of Lodore, Goosenecks, Cataract Canyon, the Grand Canyon, and Black Canyon. Images of rock formations include the Sentinels in Canyonlands National Park. Images of dams include Fontenelle Dam, Glen Canyon Dam, Hoover Dam, Davis Dam, Parker Dam, Palo Verde Diversion Dam, Imperial Diversion Dam, and Morelos Dam. Images of reservoirs include Fontenelle Reservoir, Flaming Gorge Reservoir, Lake Powell, Lake Mead, Lake Mohave, and Lake Havasu, as well as a view of the natural lake, Grand Lake. Images of bridges across the Colorado River include Dewey Bridge, Navajo Bridge, and Silver Bridge.
  - 1. Lodore Canyon, Dinosaur National Monument, Colorado, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2. Split Mountain, Dinosaur National Monument, Utah, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 3. Browns Park National Wildlife Refuge, Colorado, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 4. Shoshone, Glenwood Canyon, Colorado, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 5. Bond, Colorado, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 6. Near Marbleton, Wyoming, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 7. Near Marbleton, Wyoming, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 8. Steamboat Rock, Dinosaur National Monument, Colorado, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 9. Gunnison Butte, near Green River, Utah, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10. Dewey Bridge, Utah, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 11. Shafer Trail, near Moab, Utah, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 12. The Gooseneck, near Canyonlands National Park, Utah, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 13. The Gooseneck, near Canyonlands National Park, Utah, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 14. The Sentinels, Canyonlands National Park, Utah, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 15. Cataract Canyon, Canyonlands National Park, Utah, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 16. Hite, Lake Powell, Utah, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 17. Hite, Lake Powell, Utah, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 18. Under Navajo Bridge, Marble Canyon, Arizona, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 19. Silver Bridge, near Phantom Ranch, Grand Canyon, Arizona, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 20. Plateau Point, Grand Canyon, Arizona, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 21. Plateau Point, Grand Canyon, Arizona, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 22. Quartermaster View, Grand Canyon, Arizona, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 23. Grand Lake, Colorado, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 24. Fontenelle Dam, Wyoming, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 25. Fontenelle Reservoir, Wyoming, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 26. Sheep Creek Bay Overlook, Flaming Gorge Reservoir, Utah, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 27. Davis Gulch, Lake Powell, Utah, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 28. Slick Rock Canyon, Lake Powell, Utah, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 29. Jackass Beach, Lake Powell, Utah, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 30. Forgotten Canyon, Lake Powell, Utah, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 31. Wahweap Marina, Lake Powell, Arizona, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 32. Wahweap Marina, Lake Powell, Arizona, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 33. Wahweap Marina, Lake Powell, Arizona, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 34. Wahweap Marina, Lake Powell, Arizona, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 35. Glen Canyon Dam, near Page, Arizona, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 36. Glen Canyon Dam and Lake Powell, near Page, Arizona, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 37. Boulder Beach, Lake Mead, Nevada, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 38. Hoover Dam, Arizona/Nevada, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 39. Hoover Dam, Arizona/Nevada, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 40. Black Canyon, Arizona/Nevada, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 41. Katherine Landing, Lake Mohave, Arizona, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 42. Davis Dam, Arizona/Nevada, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 43. Davis Dam, Arizona/Nevada, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 44. Black Meadow Landing, Lake Havasu, California, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 45. Parker Dam, near Parker, Arizona, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 46. Palo Verde Dam, near Palo Verde, California, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 47. Imperial Dam, near Yuma, Arizona, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 48. Morelos Dam, Algodones, Sonora, Mexico, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 49. Near Palo Verde, California, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - 50. Big River, California, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - 51. Angus Wilson Bridge, from the California side of the Colorado River, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 52. Water Wheel Resort, near Blythe, California, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 53. Big River, California, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 54. Near Winterhaven, California, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 55. Near Parker, Arizona, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 56. Near Parker, Arizona, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 57. Below Imperial Dam on the California side of the Colorado River, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 58. Below Imperial Dam on the California side of the Colorado River, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 59. Pipeline at Gene Pumping Plant just south of Parker Dam on the California side of the Colorado River, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 60. Near San Luis, Sonora, Mexico, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Panoramic Prints
    - Hoover Dam, Arizona/Nevada, 1995 (Box 19)
    - Lake Havasu, California, undated (Box 20)
- Basin & Range, 1987-2004; Series II; 0.75; (9 boxes)
  Photographs of Basin & Range, 1987-2004, consists of images created by Halverson that explore a semiarid region of the western United States, also known as the Great Basin. This region extends from the Sierra Nevada on the west to the Wasatch Range on the east and from the Columbia Plateau in the north to the Mojave Desert in the south. Images from this region include sites in Arizona, California, Montana, Nevada, Utah, and Wyoming, as well as two views of Shiprock, New Mexico. Photographs of Arizona include Benson, Lake Powell, and Quartzite. Photographs of California include Alabama Hills, Desert Hot Springs, Independence, Keeler, Olancha, and Saline Valley, as well as several sites in Death Valley including Badwater, Death Valley Junction, Furnace Creek, and Teakettle Junction. Photographs of Montana include Dupuyer, Lennep, and an area near Heart Butte. Photographs of Nevada include the Elko, North Las Vegas, Pyramid Lake, Rhyolite, Tonopah, and Winnemucca. Photographs of Utah include Bonneville Salt Flats, Cathedral Valley in Capitol Reef National Park, Crescent Junction, Factory Butte, Hite, Great Salt Lake, Great Salt Lake Desert, Monument Valley, Price, and Valley of the Gods. Photographs of Wyoming include Cora, Dubois, Greybull, Pinedale, Reliance, Rock Springs, Thermopolis, Wind River, and Yellowstone National Park.
  - 1. Route 6 near Green River, Utah, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 2. Near Independence, California, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 3. Greybull, Wyoming, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 4. Death Valley Junction, California, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 5. Pyramid Lake, Nevada, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 6. Dupuyer, Montana, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 7. Lake Powell near Page, Arizona, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 8. Furnace Creek, Death Valley, California, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 9. Furnace Creek, Death Valley, California, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 10. Furnace Creek, Death Valley, California, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 11. Cora, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - 12. Dubois, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - 13. Winnemucca, Nevada, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - 14. Saline Valley, California, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - 15. Bonneville Salt Flats, Utah, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - 16. Great Salt Lake, Utah, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - 17. Near Heart Butte, Montana, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - 18. Dubois, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - 19. Near Elko, Nevada, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - 20. Greybull, Wyoming, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - 21. Crescent Junction, Utah, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - 22. Interstate 80, Great Salt Desert, Utah, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - 23. Near Benson, Arizona, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - 24. Teakettle Junction, Death Valley, California, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - 25. Near Olancha, California, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - 26. Near Price, Utah, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - 27. Cathedral Valley, Utah, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - 28. Rhyolite, Nevada, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - 29. Pinedale, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - 30. Along Route 50, Central Nevada, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - 31. Near Dubois, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - 32. Rock Springs, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - 33. Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - 34. Badwater, Death Valley, California, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - 35. Monument Valley, Utah, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - 36. Thermopolis, Wyoming, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - 37. Reliance, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - 38. Wind River, Wyoming, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - 39. Valley of the Gods, Utah, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - 40. Along Route 190 near Keeler, California, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - 41. Near Factory Butte, Utah, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - 42. Along Route 190 near Keeler, California, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - 43. Cora, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - 44. Near Pyramid Lake, Nevada, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - 45. Quartzite, Arizona, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - 46. Near Dubois, Wyoming, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - 47. Cathedral Valley, Utah, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - 48. Near Tonopah, Nevada, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - 49. Saline Valley, California, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - 50. Lake Powell, Navajo Mountain, Navajo Power Plant, Arizona/Utah, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - 51. Alabama Hills, near Lone Pine, California, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - 52. Desert Hot Springs, California, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - 53. North Las Vegas, Nevada, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - 54. Monument Valley, Utah, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - 55. Lennep, Montana, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - 56. Badwater, Death Valley, California, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - 57. Badwater, Death Valley, California, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - 58. Shiprock, New Mexico, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - 59. Hite, Lake Powell, Utah, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - 60. Shiprock, New Mexico, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Panoramic Photographs
    - Furnace Creek, Death Valley, California, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Rhyolite, Nevada, 2004 (Box 22)
    - Saline Valley, California, 2004 (Box 23)
    - Shiprock, New Mexico, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Thermopolis, Wyoming, 1992 (Box 25)
- Mulholland: Nature and Culture in Los Angeles, 1991-2006; Series III; 0.88; (10 boxes)
  Arranged sequentially by numbers applied by Halverson, followed by panoramic photographs also arranged sequentially.
  Mulholland: Nature and Culture in Los Angeles, 1991-2006, depicts views along Mulholland Highway and Mulholland Drive, a scenic road in Los Angeles County, California, that runs from California Highway 1 (Pacific Coast Highway) near Malibu along the crest of the Santa Monica Mountains to Hollywood. The route provides access, directly or en-route, to many of the regional parks in the Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area. Locations depicted in the photographs are arranged sequentially from west to east. Identified communities include Beverly Glen, Calabasas Highlands, and Universal City, as well as a view above the Hollywood Bowl. Images of canyons or their vicinity include Laurel Canyon, Fryman Canyon, and Runyon Canyon. Images of reservoirs include Encino Reservoir, Stone Canyon Reservoir, and Hollywood Reservoir. Many of the photographs show the scenic road near or at intersections with other roads.
  - 1. Mulholland near Pacific Coast Highway, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - 2. Mulholland near Pacific Coast Highway, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - 3. Mulholland near Pacific Coast Highway, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - 4. Mulholland near Pacific Coast Highway, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - 5. Mulholland near Little Sycamore Canyon Road, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - 6. Mulholland near Little Sycamore Canyon Road, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - 7. Mulholland near Kanan Road, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - 8. Mulholland near Kanan Road, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - 9. Mulholland near Kanan Road, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - 10. Mulholland near Kanan Road, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - 11. Mulholland near Las Virgenes Road, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - 12. Mulholland near Las Virgenes Road, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - 13. Mulholland near Las Virgenes Road, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - 14. Mulholland near Las Virgenes Road, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - 15. Mulholland near Calabasas Highlands, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - 16. Mulholland near Las Virgenes Road, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - 17. Mulholland near Calabasas Highlands, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - 18. Mulholland at Dry Creek Cold Canyon Road, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - 19. Mulholland at Dry Creek Cold Canyon Road, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - 20. Mulholland at Dry Creek Cold Canyon Road, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - 21. Mulholland at Dry Creek Cold Canyon Road, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - 22. Mulholland near Kanan Dume Road, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - 23. Mulholland near Woodcliff Road, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - 24. Mulholland above Encino Reservoir, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - 25. Mulholland above Stone Canyon Reservoir, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - 26. Mulholland near Beverly Glen, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - 27. Mulholland near Beverly Glen, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - 28. Mulholland at Beverly Glen, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - 29. Mulholland at Beverly Glen, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - 30. Mulholland near Beverly Glen, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - 31. Mulholland near Beverly Glen, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - 32. Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - 33. Mulholland near Coldwater Canyon, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - 34. Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - 35. Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - 36. Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - 37. Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - 38. Mulholland near Laurel Canyon, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 158)
  - 39. Mulholland at Fryman Canyon Overlook, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - 40. Mulholland near Laurel Canyon, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - 41. Mulholland at Universal City Overlook, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - 42. Mulholland near Laurel Canyon, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - 43. Mulholland overlooking Universal City, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - 44. Mulholland near Wrightwood Drive, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - 45. Mulholland near Woodrow Wilson Drive, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - 46. Mulholland at Multiview Drive, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - 47. Mullholland near Woodrow Wilson Drive, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 167)
  - 48. Mulholland near Woodrow Wilson Drive, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - 49. Mulholland near Runyon Canyon, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 169)
  - 50. Mulholland near Runyon Canyon, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 170)
  - 51. Mulholland at Mulholland Scenic Corridor, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - 52. Mulholland above Hollywood Bowl, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - 53. Mulholland near Cahuenga Boulevard, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - 54. Mulholland near Cahuenga Boulevard, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - 55. Mulholland near Cahuenga Boulevard, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - 56. Mulholland near Cahuenga Boulevard, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - 57. Mulholland at Cahuenga Boulevard, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - 58. Mulholland above Hollywood Reservoir, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - 59. Mulholland at Durand Drive, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - 60. Mulholland at Canyon Lake Drive, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Panoramic Photographs
    - Mulholland near Pacific Coast Highway, 1991 (Box 26)
    - Mulholland near Skyline Drive, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Mulholland overlooking Universal City, 1991 (Box 28)
    - Mulholland near Runyon Canyon, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Mulholland near Cahuenga Pass, 1992 (Box 30)